{
    "subject": "resource/Poultrygeist:_Night_of_the_Chicken_Dead",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is a 2006 zombie comedy/horror musical-exploitation film from Troma Entertainment, directed by Lloyd Kaufman and co-directed by former long-time Troma editor Gabriel Friedman from a screenplay by Friedman and Daniel Bova. The film opened to positive reviews from Entertainment Weekly, and The New York Times,. Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead was released in 2006 in theaters and in 2008 on DVD.",
    "human_readable": "The comment for Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is that it's a 2006 zombie comedy/horror musical-exploitation film from Troma Entertainment, directed by Lloyd Kaufman and co-directed by former long-time Troma editor Gabriel Friedman from a screenplay by Friedman and Daniel Bova. The film opened to positive reviews from Entertainment Weekly, and The New York Times. It was released in 2006 in theaters and in 2008 on DVD.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9263052344322205,
            "question": "Who co-directed Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9217957854270935,
            "question": "Who directed Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9170318245887756,
            "question": "Who co-wrote the screenplay for Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9158524870872498,
            "question": "What publication gave positive reviews to Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8685961365699768,
            "question": "Which entertainment company produced Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8435911536216736,
            "question": "What year was Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead released in theaters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389543294906616,
            "question": "What year was Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead released on DVD?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8016696572303772,
            "question": "What film genre does Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead primarily fall into?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995341420173645,
            "question": "Besides theaters, in what format was Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7818407416343689,
            "question": "What is unique about the combination of genres in Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment for Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is that it's a 2006 zombie comedy/horror musical-exploitation film from Troma Entertainment, directed by Lloyd Kaufman and co-directed by former long-time Troma editor Gabriel Friedman from a screenplay by Friedman and Daniel Bova. The film opened to positive reviews from Entertainment Weekly, and The New York Times. It was released in 2006 in theaters and in 2008 on DVD.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1518_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides theaters, in what format was Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1518_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film genre does Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead primarily fall into?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1518_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead released on DVD?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1518_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1518_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe query asks whether the information in the documents supports the comment about Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead being a 2006 zombie comedy/horror musical-exploitation film from Troma Entertainment, directed by Lloyd Kaufman and co-directed by former long-time Troma editor Gabriel Friedman from a screenplay by Friedman and Daniel Bova.\n\nThe answer is \"yes\" because this information is explicitly stated in multiple documents:\n\n* In document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1518/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt`, it is mentioned that Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is a \"2006 musical comedy horror film from Troma Entertainment, directed by Lloyd Kaufman from a screenplay by Gabriel Friedman and Daniel Bova.\"\n* In document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1518/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt`, it is mentioned that Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is a \"sly mix of social satire, extreme gore, slapstick comedy and toe-tapping musical numbers\", which suggests that it is also a comedy/horror film.\n* In document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1518/re-ranker-msmarco/107.txt`, it is mentioned that the film was \"filmed here in Buffalo, rather than in New Jersey\", but this does not contradict the other information.\n\nTherefore, the output is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The documents support the fact that Poultrygeist: Night of the Chicken Dead is a 2006 film from Troma Entertainment directed by Lloyd Kaufman and co-directed by Gabriel Friedman, with a screenplay by Friedman and Daniel Bova.\n- While specific mentions of positive reviews from Entertainment Weekly or The New York Times are not present in the provided documents, the documents do confirm it was released in theaters in 2006 and on DVD in 2008. The description aligns well with it being a zombie comedy/horror musical-exploitation film.\n- The term \"musical\" is also mentioned in some of the texts, supporting this aspect as well."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}